[

{
    
        "question": "Q1 => CPU stand for",
        "answer": "Central Process Unit",
        "options": [
            "Central Program Unit",
            "Central Process Unit",
            "Central page Unit",
            "None of these"
        ]
    
},
{
   "question": "Q2 => Full form of OS is",
   "answer": "Operating system",
   "options":[
    "Order of significance",
    "Operating system",
    "Open software",
   "Optical Sensor"
    
   ]

    

},
{
    "question": "Q3 => The ribbon is used in",
    "answer": "Dot Matrix printe",
    "options":[
     "Laser Printer",
     "Plotter",
     "Ink-jet printer",
    "Dot Matrix printe"
 
    ]

},
{
    "question": "Q4 => Address book contains",
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "options":[
     "Email address",
     "Phone numbers",
     "People Names",
    "All of the above"
 
    ]

},
{
    "question": "Q5 => Joystick is used to",
    "answer": "Both a and b",
    "options":[
     "Move cursor on the screen",
     "Computer games",
     "Both a and b",
    "None of these"
 
    ]

},
{
    "question": "Q6=> What type of memory is volatile",
    "answer": "RAM",
    "options":[
     "RAM",
     "ROM",
     "CASHE",
    "None of these"
 
    ]

},
{
    "question": "Q7 => Main memory is also known as ",
    "answer": "Primery memory",
    "options":[
     "Auxiliary memory",
     "Primery memory",
     "Secondry memory",
    "None of these"
 
    ]

},
{
    "question": "Q8 => For reproducing sound the CD audio player uses a ",
    "answer": "Laser Beam",
    "options":[
     "Quartz Cristal",
     "Titanium Needle",
     "Laser Beam",
    "None of these"
 
    ]

},

{
    "question": "Q9 => Which of the following would indicate that the motherboard battery has failed  ",
    "answer": "Hardware settings, including the current date and time reverts to default values",
    "options":[
     "Operating system passwords are lost",
     "Files on the hard disk are lost and corrupted",
     "Hardware settings, including virtual memory reverts to default values ",
    "Hardware settings, including the current date and time reverts to default values"
 
    ]

},
{
    "question": "Q10 => What is MAC ",
    "answer": "Media Access Control",
    "options":[
     "A computer made by Apple",
     "Memory address corruption",
     "Mediocre Apple Computer",
    "Media Access Control"
 
    ]

}
]